MICHALIS KITSAKIS

Marousi, Athens Mobile: 6981997400 e-mail: kitsakis m@yahoo.gr

https://github.com/Michalis-Dev

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Experienced professional with over 15 years in designing, developing, testing, maintaining electronic circuits and development industrial software's. Familiar with computer design and engineering software to create project plans and circuit diagram (PCB) by following the electrical and construction safety regulations. Able to work with versatility and discipline as well as initiative and creative way of thinking, constantly seeking, finding and implementing the simplest solution to the most complex problems.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ελληνική Αναπτυξιακή Τράπεζα "HDB" Software Engineer

• IT Department- Developer.

Comtel S.A

November 2010 to August 2022

August 2022 until now

Electronic Engineer

- Maintenance and monitoring of Public Warning System projects.
- R&D in projects according to customer's requirement.
- Designing circuits and create PCB using Eagle PCB Design Software | Autodesk.
- Testing and Quality Control of PCBs, Power Amplifier circuit, Power Supplies and RF Signal,
 Digital transceiver Motorola.
- Study acoustic coverage with Sound Propagation Emulator in 3D (SoundPLAN).
- Designing network and configuration microwave device (Ubiquiti, Mikrotik PtP PtMP link).
- Configuration digital radio and create RF network (Mototrbo).
- Maintenance and monitoring as required of the project.

ACHIEVEMENTS:

- Design database with personal details from employees of Ministry Education of Iraq.
- Design and installation dedicated email system communicate only with HF radio.
- Design and development product for streaming audio and send / receive data over IP.
- Develop and design short range wireless (868MHz).
- Certification process for CE, LVD (Low Voltage Directive), EMC (Electromagnetic Compatibility), RED (Radio Equipment Directive).
- Creating test process for electronic product.
- Organization of small production line PCB.

National Center for Research "Demokritos" Electronic Engineer

August 2009 to October 2010

• Technical support and operation of the Ion implantation Eaton NV3204.

Credicom Help desk support December 2008 to August 2009

mobile: (+30) 6981997400

kitsakis m@yahoo.gr https://github.com/Michalis-Dev

EFG Eurobank Ergasias

May 2006 to November 2008

Technical Support

- Configuration and operation Neopost Mailing machine.
- Backup for each employee workstation (Acronis, Cobian)

Goody's

July 2005 to April 2006

mobile: (+30) 6981997400

Staff

- Fast food preparation and assembly.
- Cashire and orders.

SKILLS

- PCB design familiar with kiCad | Eagle Autodesk.
- Knowledge of programming language (java, Python, C/C++).
- Create various project with STM32 or PIC32.
- Strong knowledge of development tools Eclipse IDE, IntelliJ IDEA.
- Development software related to products or internal software/hardware custom projects with JavaFX/FXML graphics.
- Knowledge HTML5, CSS3 and PHP
- Knowledge of database MySQL and Access.
- Debugging, unit test.
- Network protocol analyzer (Wireshark).
- Troubleshooting, network problems, build simple and complex networks.
- Installation and configuration IP phones, switches and routers.
- Installation and manage domain controller, File Server and Print Server.
- Network diagrams using Microsoft Visio and simulate with Packet Tracer.
- Monitoring and Maintenance database, plans for backups, index rebuild/defragment, and database statistics

Education

Open Hellenic University

Postgraduate "Specialization in information Systems"

ASETEM/SELETE

Bachelor degree: Department of Mechanical Engineering Educators

Certifications

- The Massachusetts Institute Technology 6.002x: Circuits and Electronics.
- National Technical University of Athens
 - Design and analyze network.
- Cisco Networking Academy

Cyber Security Training.

Addition information

Born in 1982, married with 2 children

Interest: PC builder, basketball, cinema, theater, travel.

Recommendation: available upon request

kitsakis m@yahoo.gr https://github.com/Michalis-Dev